Inventory of the Papers of Edwin S. Cohen
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Foreign Files
  - Bank Accounts: Secrecy, Bilateral Assistance, 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box 52)
  - Bank Accounts: Secrecy, Bilateral Assistance, 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - British Tax Reform, 1970 (Box 53)
  - Canada Tax Reform, 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 53)
  - Canada Tax Reform, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Canada Tax Reform. Visit of Canadian Finance Minister Benson. [With 5 Canadian books about their tax reform], 1971 (Box 54)
  - Charities Official Investment Fund [COIF], 1970 (Box 54)
  - Controlled Foreign Corporations, 1969-1970 (Box 54)
  - Council on International Economic Policy Operations Group [CIEP], 1971 (Box 55)
  - Depletion Percentage, 1969-1972 (Box 55)
  - Deposits in U.S. Banks, 1969 (Box 55)
  - Direct Investment Program, 1969-1971 (Box 55)
  - DISC [Domestic International Sales Corporation], 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - DISC, 1969-1972, 5 folders (Box 56)
  - DISC, 1969-1972, 5 folders (Box 57)
  - DISC Basic Materials, 1969-1972, 5 folders (Box 58)
  - DISC-GATT, 1972 (Box 59)
  - DISC-hold, 1972 (Box 59)
  - DISC Marginal Cost, 1972 (Box 59)
  - DISC Miscellaneous Materials, 1969-1981 (Box 59)
  - DISC Miscellaneous Documents, 1969-1981 (Box 59)
  - DISC. National-Foreign Trade Convention, 1969 (Box 59)
  - DISC Pamphlet, 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 59)
  - DISC Workshop. Los Angeles, Calif., 1972 (Box 59)
  - Export Incentives, 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 60)
  - Expropriation Losses. Cuba, 1971-1972 (Box 60)
  - Foreign Income, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Foreign Income Advisory Group, 1969 (Box 61)
  - Foreign Investors Tax Act, 1969-1979 (Box 61)
  - Foreign Tax Credits, 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Foreign Trade General Documents, 1970-1973, 1 folder (Box 61)
  - Foreign Trade General Documents, 1970-1973, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - GATT Border Tax Adjustments, 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - German Tax Reform, 1971-1973 (Box 62)
  - Group of Four-U.S. Tax Cooperation (2 folders and 2 booklets of meetings), 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - Interamerican Center of Tax Administration. Presentation on the Foreign Tax Assistance Program, 1967-1969 (Box 63)
  - Interest Equalization Tax, 1968-1971, 2 folders (Box 64)
  - International Monetary System: IMF, IBRD, IFC, IDA, 1972 (Box 64)
  - International Mutual Fund Operations, 1970-1972 (Box 64)
  - Investment Recovery Allowances-LDC, 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Israel Foreign Exchange Position, 1969 (Box 64)
  - Italian Tax Reform, 1971 (Box 64)
  - Italian Tax Reform. Cohen's visit to Rome, 1969-1971 (Box 64)
  - International Shipping Income, 1971 (Box 64)
  - IRS § 367; § 269, 1969-1971 (Box 64)
  - Latin America Tax Recommendations, 1969-1971 (Box 65)
  - Lend-a-Star Problem: Citizens employed by International Organizations. Minimum Distributions. Non Resident Alien Taxation, 1969-1971 (Box 65)
  - Oil Countries, 1969-1972 (Box 65)
  - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development [OECD], 1971-1973, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - OECD Committee on Fiscal Affairs, 1972 (Box 65)
  - OECD Observer, 1972 (Box 65)
  - OECD Revenue Statistics of Members Countries, 1968-1970 (Box 65)
  - Philippines, Tax Policy Telegram, 1971 (Box 66)
  - Puerto Rico Tax Reform Project, 1971-1972 (Box 66)
  - Sugar Tax Legislation, 1971 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: African Countries, 1972 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: Australia, 1969-1971 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: Belgium, 1969-1971 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: Brazil, 1972 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: Canada, 1969-1972 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: China, Cyprus, Denmark, 1971-1972 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: Finland, 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: France, 1969-1973 (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties: Germany, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Tax Treaties General Documents, 1969-1972 (Box 67)
  - Tax Treaties: Guam, 1969-1970 (Box 67)
  - Tax Treaties: Hong Kong, Iran, Israel, Ivory Cost, 1969-1972 (Box 67)
  - Tax Treaties: Indonesia, 1969-1972 (Box 67)
  - Tax Treaties: Jamaica, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 67)
  - Tax Treaties: Japan, 1969-1972 (Box 67)
  - Tax Treaties: Korea, Malaysia, Morocco, Surinam, Taiwan, 1972 (Box 67)
  - Tax Treaties: Netherlands, 1969-1972 (Box 68)
  - Tax Treaties: New Zealand, Uruguay, 1971 (Box 68)
  - Tax Treaties: Norway, 1970-1972 (Box 68)
  - Tax Treaties: Philippines, Pakistan, Poland, Romania, Singapore, Spain, Turkey, 1971-1972 (Box 68)
  - Tax Treaties: Soviet Union, 1972 (Box 68)
  - Tax Treaties: Switzerland, 1969-1973 (Box 68)
  - Tax Treaties: Trinidad and Tobago, 1970 (Box 69)
  - Tax Treaties: United Kingdom, 1969-1973 (Box 69)
  - Tax Treaties: United Nations Ad Hoc Expert Group on Tax Treaties between Developed and Developing Countries, 1969-1970 (Box 69)
  - U.S. Investments Abroad, 1972, 3 folders (Box 69)
  - U.S. Investments Abroad, 1972, 1 folder (Box 70)
  - U.S. Possessions Tax Problems, 1969-1970 (Box 70)
  - Value Added Tax [VAT], 1969-1971, 3 folders (Box 70)
  - VAT, 1969-1971, 3 folders (Box 71)
  - VAT Denmark, 1968-1969 (Box 71)
  - VAT Miscellaneous Documents, 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - VAT Miscellaneous Documents, 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Value Added Tax in the United States, its Implications for Retailers, 1970 (Box 72)
  - Western Hemisphere Trade Corporation [WHTC]. Zambia: Taxation Convention, 1972 (Box 72)
- Personal Files
  - ABA Planning Commission, 1970-1972 (Box 73)
  - Asset Depreciation Range System [ADR] Publication, 1971 (Box 73)
  - ADR. Tax Depreciation Policy Options. Measures of Effectiveness and Estimated Revenue Losses, [1971] (Box 73)
  - ADR-Treasury Department Press Releases, 1971 (Box 73)
  - ADR Comments. Major Legal Submissions, [1971] (Box 73)
  - ADR Comments A through Z (2 notebooks), [1971] (Box 74)
  - ADR Hearings. Transcript of Proceedings (3 books), 1971 (Box 75)
  - American Law Institute, 1971 (Box 75)
  - Articles. Requests for magazines and some articles, 1969-1972 (Box 75)
  - Cohen's Gray Diary, 1970 (Box 76)
  - Congratulatory Letters on his Appointment as Assistant Secretary of the Treasury, 1969 (Box 76)
  - Department of the Treasury. Tax Policy Personnel, 1969-1972 (Box 76)
  - Investment Company Institute [ICI]. First Case, 1968-1971 (Box 76)
  - ICI Book, 1968-1969 (Box 76)
  - ICI Miscellaneous File, 1967-1969 (Box 76)
  - Invitations, 1969-1972, 4 folders (Box 77)
  - Knollwood Cemetery File (Knollwood vs. IRS Case), 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous Files: Legal Cases, Virginia State Tax Matters, Special Committee on Substantive Tax Reform, 1969-1970 (Box 78)
  - Nixon Task Force on Task Legislation, 1968, 3 folders (Box 78)
  - Nixon Task Force on Tax Policy. White House Request, 1969 (Box 78)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1969-1972, 5 folders (Box 79)
  - Personal Correspondence. Outgoing Mail, 1970-1971, 5 folders (Box 80)
  - Personal Correspondence. Outgoing Mail, 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 81)
  - Presidential Directives Received from the White House, 1969 (Box 81)
  - Republican National Committee and Platform, 1970, 1972 (Box 81)
  - Task Force on Tax Legislation Report, 1968 (Box 81)
  - Tax Forum. The Tax Club, 1969-1972 (Box 82)
  - Telephone Calls, 1970-1971, 3 folders (Box 82)
  - Treasury Submission to Republican Platform, 1972 (Box 82)
  - UVA Computer Tax Studies, 1969 (Box 82)
  - Virginia Income Tax Commission, 1970 (Box 83)
  - Virginia Income Tax Commission Study Committee, 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 83)
  - Capital Gains Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 84)
  - Department of the Treasury General Briefing Manual, 1969 (Box 84)
  - Employee Benefits Briefing Book, 1970 (Box 84)
  - Estate and Gift Tax Briefing Books (5 vols.), [1970] (Box 85)
  - Financial Institutions. Senate Finance Committee Executive Sessions, 1969 (Box 86)
  - Foundation Report Hearings Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 86)
  - Industrial Development Bonds (furnishing of electrical energy) Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 86)
  - [International Tax Treaties] Data Book. (And notes for talk to foreign tax assistance teams, Fredericksburg, Va.), 1969 (Box 87)
  - International Tax Proposals Briefing Book, 1971 (Box 87)
  - [International Tax Treaties] U.S.- Jamaica Briefing Book, 1971 (Box 87)
  - [International Tax Treaties] U.S.- Norway Briefing Book, 1972 (Box 87)
  - [International] Tax Treaties Hearing on Japan and France Briefing Book. Nondiscrimination under Jamaican Treaty, 1971 (Box 88)
  - [International Tax Treaties] Netherlands, Trinidad, Finland & Belgium, 1970 (Box 88)
  - Members' Bill Briefing Book (Vol. 1), 1970 (Box 88)
  - Members' Bill Briefing Book (Vol. 2), 1970 (Box 89)
  - North Atlantic Council Meeting Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 89)
  - Private Foundations Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 89)
  - Revenue Estimates Briefing Book, 1971 (Box 90)
  - Revenue Estimating Procedure (including section on overwithholding problem) Briefing Book, 1972 (Box 90)
  - Statistics of Income. Business Income Tax Returns Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 90)
  - Surcharge and Investment Credit Repeal Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 90)
  - Tax Exempt Organizations Briefing Book, 1970 (Box 91)
  - Tax Exempt Organizations (H. R. 13270) Briefing Book, 1970 (Box 91)
  - Tax Program (Capital Gains) Briefing Book, 1972 (Box 91)
  - Tax Reform Hearings Ways and Means Committee Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 91)
  - Tax Reform Studies and Proposals Briefing Books (2 notebooks), 1969 (Box 92)
  - Tax Reform Proposals. General and Technical Explanation (2 vols.), 1969 (Box 93)
  - Tax Reform Act. Accumulation Trusts and Grantor Trusts. Multiple Corporations. Stock Dividends Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 94)
  - Tax Reform Act. Amendments and tentative drafts, 1969 (Box 94)
  - Tax Reform Act. Charitable Contributions. Farm Losses, etc. Limitation on Interest Deduction Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 95)
  - Tax Reform Act. Employer Benefits. LTP and Allocation of Deductions. Income Averaging Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 95)
  - Tax Reform Act. Foreign Briefing Book. Depreciation of Public Utility Property. Earnings and Profits, Accelerated Depreciation. Cooperatives, 1969 (Box 96)
  - Tax Reform Act. Tax Relief Briefing Book (Low Income Allowance, etc.) Revenue Effects, Estimates, etc., 1969 (Box 96)
  - Tax Reform Act. Real Estate. Pollution Control, Railroads. Continental Shelf Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 97)
  - THINK-IN on Estate and Gift Taxes Briefing Book, 1970 (Box 97)
  - Transition Material, 1969 (Box 97)
  - Travel Tax, etc. Proposals Briefing Book, 1968 (Box 97)
  - Value Added Tax Briefing Book, 1969 (Box 98)
  - Briefing Book prepared by the White House Staff. State of the Union Message, 1971 (Box 98)
- Miscellaneous Files
  - ABA Section of Taxation Recommendations, 1969, 2 folders (Box 99)
  - ACIR [Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations] Advisory Tax, 1979-1972 (Box 99)
  - Alumina Bauxite Pricing. Jamaica Bauxite Cases, 1970-1972, folders 1 - 2 of 5 (Box 99)
  - Alumina Bauxite Pricing. Jamaica Bauxite Cases, 1970-1972, folders 3 - 5 of 5 (Box 100)
  - [Chilean Expropriation of Copper Mines] Miscellaneous Papers, 1971 (Box 100)
  - Corporations Effective Rate of Tax, 1972 (Box 100)
  - Debt Ceiling Increase. Individuals Effective Rate of Tax, 1972 (Box 100)
  - Discussions with Assistant Secretary Betts, 1970-1971 (Box 100)
  - Discuss with Secretary Conally. Lists of Treasury Consultants, 1971 (Box 100)
  - ESC [Edwin S. Cohen] Miscellaneous Papers], 1971 (Box 101)
  - Estate and Gift Taxes, 1969-1972 (Box 101)
  - Fort Sam Houston, 1972 (Box 101)
  - International Fiscal Association, 1969-1973, 2 folders (Box 101)
  - International Monetary Problems, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 102)
  - McGovern Position on Taxes, 1969-1972 (Box 102)
  - Memorandum for the files. Memorandum for the Deputy Secretary, 1969-1972 (Box 102)
  - Memos to the Secretary, weekly reports, goals and objectives, 1969-1971 (Box 102)
  - Memoranda to the Undersecretary. Miscellaneous Papers, 1960-1972 (Box 102)
  - Memoranda for the President and Assistants to the President, 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 103)
  - Memoranda for the Secretary of the Treasury, 1970-1973, 2 folders (Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1971 (Box 103)
  - Report of the Committee on Organization of the Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box 104)
  - Tax Credits-Poverty, 1968-1969 (Box 104)
  - [Tax] Miscellaneous Papers, 1969-1971 (Box 104)
  - Value Added Tax. Chronological. Confidential, 1970-1971 (Box 104)
  - Tax Laws Revision. Miscellaneous Documents (2 notebooks), 1972 (Box 105)
- Speeches File
  - ABA Annual Meeting. Dallas, TX., 1969 (Box 106)
  - ABA Mid-year Meeting. Tax Section, New Orleans, 1971 (Box 106)
  - ABA National Institutes, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1970 (Box 106)
  - ABA Tax Section, London, England, 1971 (Box 106)
  - ALI-ABA Course Study on Professional Corporations, Insurance and Qualified Plans, 1972 (Box 106)
  - American Bankers Association. 51st Midwinter Trust Conference, New York, 1970 (Box 106)
  - American Horse Council, Pampano Beach, Florida, 1971 (Box 106)
  - American Institute of CPA's, Atlanta, Ga. Boston Educational TV (Channel 2), 1969 (Box 106)
  - American Institute od CPA's Annual Meeting, New York, 1970 (Box 107)
  - American Iron and Steel Institute, Point Clear, Ala., 1969 (Box 107)
  - American Management Association and the International Fiscal Association, New York, 1972 (Box 107)
  - American Pension Conference, New York, 1970 (Box 107)
  - 25th Annual Institute on Federal Taxation. USC Law Center, Los Angeles, CA. National Export Expansion Council, 1972 (Box 107)
  - 28th Annual Institute on Federal Taxation, New York University, 1969 (Box 107)
  - Arizona State University Tax Institute, 1970 (Box 107)
  - BNA [Bureau of National Affairs] Tax Management Conference, New York, 1971 (Box 107)
  - The Business Council, Hot Spring, Va., 1972 (Box 107)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the U.S., Washington, D.C. Tax Institute of America, Raleigh, NC., 1972 (Box 107)
  - Council of Profit Sharing Industries, Pasadena, Calif., 1971 (Box 107)
  - Department of Commerce Exporters' Textile Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 107)
  - Department of the Treasury DISC Speaking Engagements, 1972 (Box 108)
  - DLJ [Donaldson, Lufkin & Jenrette, Inc.] Annual Corporate Pension Conference, New York, 1972 (Box 108)
  - Federal Executive Institute, Charlottesville, Va., 1971 (Box 108)
  - Federal Tax Institute of New England, Boston, Mass. TV Interview, 1969-1972 (Box 108)
  - House and Ways Committee on the President Tax Program, 1969 (Box 108)
  - International Fiscal Association, Los Angeles, Calif. ABA Tax Section, Washington, D.C. Subcommittee on Government Procurement of House Select Committee on Small Business. Washington Pension Report Group, 1972 (Box 108)
  - International Tax Conference, Jamaica, 1972 (Box 108)
  - International Tax Conference, Nassau, Bahamas, 1970 (Box 108)
  - Institute on State Planning, University of Miami Law School, 1970 (Box 109)
  - Investment Bankers Association of America [IBA], San Antonio, Tx, 1970 (Box 109)
  - IRS Meetings and Orientations, Washington, D.C., 1971 (Box 109)
  - IRS Statistics Division. Unpublished data from Statistics of Income 1970. Individual Income Tax Returns, 1972 (Box 109)
  - IRS Team Leader Conference, Fredericksburg, Va., 1969 (Box 109)
  - Joint Economic Committee Testimony, 1972, 2 folders (Box 109)
  - Kentucky Tax Institute, Louisville, Ky, 1972 (Box 109)
  - Machinery and Allied Products Institute [MAPI] Seminar, Washington, D.C., 1972 (Box 110)
  - Mid-America World Trade Conference, Chicago, Ill., 1972 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1966 (Box 110)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence of Meetings Attended, 1969 (Box 110)
  - National Association of Accountants, Richmond, Va., 1972 (Box 110)
  - National Association of Manufacturers [NAM], Committee on Taxation, 1970 (Box 110)
  - National Tax Association, Boston, Mass., 1969 (Box 110)
  - National Tax Association Seminar, Washington, D.C., 1971 (Box 110)
  - National Urban Coalition Round Table, Washington, D.C., 1969 (Box 110)
  - New York City Bar Association Fora, 1970 (Box 110)
  - New York State Bar Association, Tax Section, 1971 (Box 110)
  - OECD, Paris and Rome, 1971 (Box 111)
  - Oregon Tax Research Annual Meeting, Portland, Or., 1972 (Box 111)
  - Practicing Law Institute, New York, 1971 (Box 111)
  - Proposed Amendments to H.R. 12272, Individual Retirement Act of 1971, and Technical Explanation of Bill before the Committee of Ways and Means U.S. House of Representatives, 1972 (Box 111)
  - Richmond Rotary Club. International Fiscal Association and American Management. Baltimore Association of Tax Counseling. Business International Round Meetings, 1971 (Box 111)
  - Senate Special Committee on Aging, 1970 (Box 111)
  - Speaking Invitations (accepted), 1969-1972 (Box 111)
  - Speaking Invitations (declined), 1969-1973, 3 folders (Box 111)
  - Speeches. Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 112)
  - Speech Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 112)
  - State Department Atlantic Council Meeting Working Papers, 1969, 2 folders (Box 112)
  - Statements before Senate Committee on Foreign Relations, 1970 (Box 112)
  - Statement before Committee on Foreign Relations on a Protocol Amending U.S.-France Income Tax Treaty and U.S.-Japan Income Treaty. Statement before the Senate Finance Committee on the Treasury's Domestic International Sales Corporation Proposal, 1970-1971 (Box 112)
  - Statement before the Senate Finance Committee on Provisions of H.R. 13270. Tax Reform Act of 1969, 1969 (Box 112)
  - Statement before the Committee of Ways and Means on H.R. 13270, 1972 (Box 112)
  - Statements of ESC before Subcommittee on Government Procurement of the House Elect Committee on Small Business; Committee on Foreign Relations of the U.S. Senate on a Proposed Income Tax Convention with Norway; Joint Economic Committee Congress of the U.S., 1972 (Box 112)
  - Task Force on Business Taxation. Report to the President, 1970 (Box 113)
  - Task Force on International Economic Policy. Republican Research Committee. White House Fellows. Connecticut Bar Association Annual Tax Planning Institute, 1972 (Box 113)
  - Tax Executives Institute, Washington, D.C., 1970 (Box 113)
  - Tax Foundation Conference, New York, 1969 (Box 113)
  - Tax Institute of America Symposium, Washington D.C., 1971 (Box 113)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1969. ESC Statement, 1969 (Box 113)
  - Texas CPA's Tax Institute, 1970 (Box 113)
  - The American Assembly, Harriman, N.Y. Tax Foundation Inc., New York, 1972 (Box 114)
  - The Business Council, Washington, D.C., 1970 (Box 114)
  - University of Chicago Law School Annual Tax Conference, 1970 (Box 114)
  - Virginia Angus School, Fredericksburg, Va. Tax Forum, University Club, New York, 1971 (Box 114)
  - Virginia Conference on Federal Taxation, Charlottesville, Va., 1970 (Box 114)
  - Young President's Seminar. Virginia Law Review Association. Farm Credit Conference, 1970 (Box 114)
- Tapes:
  - Tax Institute of America Symposium, Washington, D.C., 1970[?]
  - Speech before Tax Forum on Revenue Act of 1971 sponsored by U.S. Chamber of Commerce, Washington, D.C., 1972
  - 4th Institute on State Planning, Miami, Fl., 1970
  - OTR Animal Meeting, n.d.
  - DISC Remarks of ESC, Los Angeles, Ca., 1972
  - MCA, Washington, D.C., 1971
  - 17th Annual Texas CPA Tax Institute, Houston, Tx, 1970
  - Swearing-in Ceremony Treasury Department, 1972
  - Annual Tax Institute, Arizona State University, 1970
  - Address to Federal Tax Institute of New England, Boston, Mass., 1972
- Private Practice and Law School Papers
  - AALS Speech 1973; ABA Section of Family and Law Speech. National Tax Association, Tax Institute of America: Tax Simplification, 1975 (Box 115)
  - ABA-ALI Section of Taxation, Special Subcommittee on ALI. Subchapter C Liaison, 1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation, Report on Corporate Distribution and Adjustments. Confidential Prints of Advisory Group, 1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation, Subchapter C. Cohen's Draft of Outline and Comments on Section 346-347, 1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Advisory Group. Problems Considered and Recommendations made with respect to Corporate Distributions and Adjustments, 1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Advisory Group. Miscellaneous Papers, 1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Committee, Section 301, drafts, comments and statements, 1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Group, Section 305, 1956-1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Committee. Sections 302 and 318, drafts, comments and statements (folder 1 of 2), 1957 (Box 115)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Committee, Sections 302 and 318. (folder 2 of 2), 1957 (Box 116)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Committee, Section 318, drafts, 1957 (Box 116)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Committee, Sections 346-371, 1957, 2 folders (Box 116)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Committee, Sections 381-382, 1957 (Box 116)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter Advisory Committee, Reorganization materials, Section 346 and mailing list, 1957 (Box 116)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Committee Group Report, 1957 (Box 117)
  - ABA Section of Taxation Subchapter C Advisory Group, 1958 (Box 117)
  - ALI-ABA Conference on Employee Benefit Plans, 1974 (Box 117)
  - ALI [American Law Institute], Corporations Reorganizations [drafts], 1957 (Box 117)
  - ALI, Federal Income, Estate and Gift Tax. Projects: 199, 202, 204, 1957 (Box 117)
  - ALI, Federal Income, Estate and Gift Tax, Projects: 205-209, 211-215, 1957 (Box 118)
  - ALI, Federal Income, Estate and Gift Tax, Project: 216-221, 224, 1957-1957 (Box 118)
  - ALI, Federal Income, Estate and Gift Tax Project. Discussion Draft No. 15, 1957 (Box 118)
  - ALI, Federal Income, Estate and Gift Tax Project. Memoranda for Discussion, Drafts Nos. 16A, 16D, 16E, 16F, 16G, 16H. Unifying Reorganizations, Attribution of Stock Ownership, Stock Bailouts, Problems of Debt in Subchapter C, Treatment of Multiple Corporations, Complete Liquidations and Collapsible Corporations (3 notebooks), 1958 (Box 118)
  - ALI, Federal Income, Estate and Gift Tax Project. Discussion Draft Nos. 19-20. Capital Gain Studies: Issues of Capital Gains Classification Considered in the Light of Basis Policies; Problems in Capital Gain Classification (Confidential, 2 notebooks), 1960 (Box 119)
  - ALI, Federal Income Tax Statute, Tentative Draft No. 4, 1951 (Box 119)
  - ALI, Federal Income Tax Statute, Discussion Draft No. 5 (Confidential), 1952 (Box 119)
  - Association of American Law Schools. Congressional Aides. ABA-Atlanta, 1976-1977 (Box 120)
  - Chesapeake Tax Conference, 1973 (Box 120)
  - Clover-Milgraum Real Estate Matter, 1968 (Box 120)
  - 1720-1979 Bank en Assurantie Associatie N.V. Worldwide. [Commemorative book of the company], 1970 (Box 120)
  - Cohen Chronological File, 1967-1969, 4 folders (Box 120)
  - Cohen Chronological File, 1967-1969, 2 folders (Box 121)
  - Cohen Files Indexes, n.d. (Box 121)
  - Cohen Personal Exams and Papers, 1929, 1936 (Box 121)
  - Commission on Private Philanthropy, 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 121)
  - Commission on Private Philanthropy, 1973-1975, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - Computers and the Law. Law Games, 1967 (Box 122)
  - Computers-Law School, 1963-1968 (Box 122)
  - Computers Print-outs, 1967 (Box 123)
  - Computer Research. Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 123)
  - Computers-Seth Sprague Educational and Charitable Foundations. Tape Rentals and Computer Time, 1967 (Box 123)
  - Computers-Substantive Tax Reform of ABA, 1967 (Box 123)
  - Computers-UVA-Law School, 1969 (Box 123)
  - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council. 31st Annual Meeting, Federal Tax Reform, Issues and Impact, 1973 (Box 123)